A Guide to the Clippings File of the University Relations Office of Information Services, 1963-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Clippings File of the University Relations Office of Information Services 1963-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/7.701, RG-4/2/7.861
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the university library in 1970 and 1986.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the Clippings File of the Office of Information Services.
Contents List
- SERIES I: Clippings 1963-1966, (RG-4/2/7.701)
  - Akins' Death 1963 (Box 1)
  - Bell, Dr. James B., Jr.--involved in hit-and-run accident in which Stephen Madigan was killed 1965 May 7 (Box 1)
  - Boyd, Alan S. 1966 (Box 1)
  - Breck, George W. (artist--Copy, School of Athens mural) 1968 (Box 1)
  - Caldwell, Erskine 1965 (Box 1)
  - Carpenter, Scott (astronaut) 1964 (Box 1)
  - Cobb Chemical Fire 1964 (Box 1)
  - College Life magazine 1965 (Box 1)
  - College Rater 1967 (Box 1)
  - Council on Human Relations--Jefferson Chapter 1965 Mar 16 (Box 1)
  - Engineering Public Information Council 1968 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly 1966 (Box 1)
  - Hootenanny--TV Folk Song Concert 1963 (Box 1)
  - Information Coordinating Board 1964 (Box 1)
  - McCall's Slander 1967 (Box 1)
  - Closing of McCormick Road 1965 (Box 1)
  - Playboy 1966 (Box 1)
  - Time (empty folder) n.d. (Box 1)
  - Trees 1966 (Box 1)
- SERIES II: Newsclippings 1978-1983, (RG-4/2/7.861)
  - Calendar of Newsclippings (6 folders) 1978-1983 (Box 1)